statsverse.com 2010-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Gamers Verse

**Privacy Statement  
GamersVerse has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for GamersVerse.**

**Information Automatically Logged**  
GamersVerse uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Our server software automatically logs all accesses to materials located on our servers. This information remains private to persons associated with GamersVerse.

**Consumer Information**  
During the process of visiting our websites, GamersVerse does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, GamersVerse does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by GamersVerse is used for the purpose of generating demographic data about our visitors.

**Data Collection**  
GamersVerse, as well as many other sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. We cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on your computer at certain times during your visits to a website. This unique data may later be recovered from your computer in order to personalize your internet experience. This cookie can help advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services.

**Advertising**  
Furthermore, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Public Forums**  
This site makes forums, downloads, articles and/or news available to its users. Please remember that any information that you choose to disclose while registering to use these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information.  GamersVerse does not and will not sell the information collected to any third parties.

**Contests**  
GamersVerse will occassionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for personal information (like name, email, and mailing address). This contact information is used only to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and is destroyed upon the completion of the contest.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. GamersVerse is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Should, in any event, any information (such as access logs) be made available to a third party, we will make the best effort to track it and report the accident to proper authorities. We cannot be held accountable for any misuse of such information.

**Contacting GamersVerse**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: privacy@gamersverse.com

See also: [Disclaimer](http://www.gamersverse.com/misc/disclaimer/)
